说实话很幸福，很幸福，一如既往的满足和享受。
The truth is very happy, very happy, content and enjoying as always.
La verdad muy feliz, muy feliz, contento y a disfrutar como siempre.
正如您的同事所说，每次通话都很特别。
Every call is special as your colleagues say.
Cada llamado es especial como dicen tus compañeros.
是啊，是啊，每一次特殊召唤，每一次特殊召唤，所以......
Yeah, yeah, every special call, every special summons, so...
Sí, sí, cada llamada especial, cada convocatoria especial, así que...
正如我常说的，享受并尽力而为。
Enjoy as I always say and do your best.
A disfrutar como digo siempre y dar lo mejor por hacer.
天使也很特别吗？
Special about Angel too?
¿Especial por lo de Ángel también?
因为迪玛利亚？
Because of Di María?
¿Por lo de Di María?
对于一切，为什么要穿这件衬衫......
For everything, why wear this shirt...
Por todo, porque vestir esta camiseta...
它涉及很多巨大的快乐。
It involves a lot and enormous joy.
implica todo muchísimo y alegría enorme.
你好吗？
How are you?
¿Cómo estás vos?
很好，完美。
Good, perfect.
Bien, perfecto.
狮子座会在这次通话中被错过吗？
Will Leo be missed in this call?
¿Se va a extrañar a Leo en esta convocatoria?
致利奥，致天使，致所有人。
To Leo, to Ángel, to everyone.
A Leo, a Ángel, a todos.
再次为阿根廷国家队效力感觉如何？
How does it feel to play here again in the Argentine national team?
¿Qué se siente volver a jugar acá en la selección argentina?
来到这里保卫我们的国家总是很高兴，很高兴。
It is always a pleasure to come here to defend our country, so happy.
Siempre es un placer venir acá a defender a nuestro país, así que contentos.
以及对安赫尔迪玛丽亚向他表示敬意的期望？
And the expectation for the tribute that Ángel Di María is going to pay him?
¿Y la expectativa por el homenaje que le van a hacer Ángel Di María?
嗯，我不知道他们准备了什么，但显然他是……
Well, I don't know what they have prepared, but obviously he is...
Bueno, no sé qué tendrán preparado, pero obviamente que él se...
他应该得到所有可能的认可，所以我们会非常享受这一切，这肯定会是一个非常激动人心的时刻。
He deserves all the recognition possible so we are going to enjoy it a lot and it will surely be a very emotional moment.
Se merece todo el reconocimiento posible así que lo vamos a disfrutar mucho y seguramente va a ser un momento de mucha emoción.
狮子座，在这次通话中我会想念你的。
I'm going to miss you Leo in this call.
Te voy a extrañar a Leo en esta convocatoria.
利奥总是很重要，但我认为他现在能做的最好的事情就是恢复得很好。
Leo is always important but I think the best thing he can do now is to recover well.
Siempre Leo es importante pero creo que lo mejor que puede hacer ahora es recuperarse bien.
我们将尽力确保这两场比赛中尽可能少的出现清真寺缺席的情况。
We will try to ensure that the absence of the cenota is as little as possible in these two games.
Nosotros trataremos de estos dos partidos, que siempre la ausencia del cenota sea lo menos posible.
至于对手，富斯特的对手是智利队，这是一场复杂的比赛，罗德里戈缺席了重要的比赛。
Regarding the rival, Fuste's rival as Chile always is, a complex match with important absences, Rodrigo.
Respecto del rival, rival de Fuste como siempre es Chile, partido complejo con ausencias importantes, Rodrigo.
南美比赛很艰难，但比分很接近。
The South American games are difficult, they are close.
Los partidos de Sudamérica son difíciles, son cerrados.
智利队在美洲杯上为我们踢了一场精彩的比赛。
Chile in the Copa América played a great game for us.
Chile en la Copa América nos hizo un gran partido.
会有点类似，因为时间不长，所以这些天我们会努力伤害他。
It will be a bit similar to that because it hasn't been long, so these days we will work to hurt him.
Será un poco similar a eso porque no pasó mucho tiempo, así que estos días trabajaremos para hacerle daño.
这是人们对美洲杯新冠军的认可，已经售罄，你将再次体验它
It is the recognition of the people for a new title in the Copa América that has already sold out and you are going to experience it again with so much
Es el reconocimiento de la gente por un nuevo título en la Copa América que ya agotó entradas y ustedes lo van a vivir nuevamente con tanta
是的，显然我们也期望如此，因为要展示......
Yes, obviously we also expect that because to show...
Sí, obviamente que también esperamos eso porque mostrar...
向所有人展示另一场美洲杯，多好啊，当我们到达时我们并没有……
Show all the people another Copa América, how good, when we arrived we didn't...
Mostrarle a toda la gente otra Copa América, que bueno, cuando llegamos no...
每个人都必须去各自的假期，所以我认为这将是第一届杯赛的美好时刻。
Everyone had to go on their respective vacations, so I think it will be a nice moment with Cup I.
cada uno se tuvo que ir a sus respectivas vacaciones, así que creo que va a ser un lindo momento con la Copa I.
也要感谢他们，他们肯定会表达感激之情。
and thank them too and surely they will show their gratitude.
y agradecerles también y seguramente ellos mostrarán su gratitud.
对于这支长期以来一直表现出色的球队来说。
to this team that has been doing so well for so long.
a este equipo que viene haciéndolo tan bien durante tanto tiempo.
没有Ángel，没有Leo，Nico可能不会成为首发，你认为自己会和乐队在一起吗？
Without Ángel, without Leo, with the possibility that Nico will not be the starter, do you see yourself with the band?
Sin Ángel, sin Leo, con la posibilidad de que Nico no sea titular, ¿te ves con la banda?
我占据了他们给我的角色，已经很多年了，我觉得
that I occupy the role that they give me, it has been many years and I feel
que ocupo el rol que me dan, ya son muchos años y me siento
这支球队的重要球员。
an important player for this team.
un jugador importante de esta selección.
这是我唯一能说的。
That's the only thing I can say.
Eso es lo único que puedo decir.
我们知道 Leo 和 Who 录像带...
We know that the Leo and who tape...
Sabemos que la cinta de Leo y quién...
以后谁来扛就看情况了，因为这支球队的队长就是他。
Whoever has to carry it later will be circumstantial because the captain of this team is him.
quien después la tenga que llevar será circunstancial porque el capitán de esta selección es él.
罗德里，在换人过程中，朱利亚诺和你一起来了。
Rodri, in the middle of the replacement, Giuliano came with you.
Rodri, en medio del recambio, Giuliano vino con ustedes.
一个加入的男孩。
A boy who joins in.
Un chico que se suma.
前几个小时你和他住在一起。
You lived previous hours with him.
Viviste horas previas con él.
你好吗？
How are you doing?
¿Cómo está?
你怎么看？
How do you see it?
¿Cómo lo ves?
好吧，一如既往，第一次询问并想知道的神经。
Well, as always the nerves of the first time asking and wanting to know.
Bueno, como siempre los nervios de la primera vez preguntando y queriendo saber.
这是他告诉你的第一件事吗？
Is this one of the first things he told you or not?
¿Esto es uno de los primeros que te contó o no?
不，名单已经出来了，我们一如既往地发现了这一点。
No, well the list came out there and we found out as always.
No, bueno salió la lista ahí y nos enteramos como siempre.
但我很高兴。
but I was very happy.
pero estaba muy feliz.
当然，这些建议可以给您带来您喜欢的建议。
Surely the advice can give you one that you enjoy.
Seguramente el consejo le puede dar uno que lo disfrute.
这并不总是发生，也不会永远持续，所以无论需要什么时间......
This doesn't always happen and it doesn't last forever, so whatever time it takes...
que esto no pasa siempre y tampoco dura para siempre, así que el tiempo que toque...
每次轮到我们来的时候，我们都必须充分享受它，这就是我们的解释。
and that it is our turn every time we come, we have to enjoy it to the fullest, that is how we have interpreted it.
y que nos toque cada vez que venimos lo tenemos que disfrutar al máximo, así lo hemos interpretado.
我认为这也是这支球队的重要组成部分，他们在球场上享受并被视为这样。
I think that is also an important part of this team, that it enjoys and is seen that way on the field.
Creo que eso también es una parte importante de este equipo, que disfruta y se lo ve así dentro de la cancha.
朱利安在马竞，他在马竞的第一天很好，非常好，显然这是他必须适应的适应……
Julián at Atlético, these first days with him at Atlético Good, very good, obviously it is an adaptation that he has to...
Julián en el Atlético, estos primeros días con él en el Atlético Bien, muy bien, obviamente es una adaptación que él tiene que...
为了满足这一要求，俱乐部付出了巨大的努力和很高的期望。
to meet, but with high expectations and the club made a great effort.
que cumplir, pero con grandes expectativas y el club hizo un esfuerzo muy grande.
因为蜘蛛和我们在一起，我们很高兴有他。
because the spider is with us, we are happy to have him.
porque la araña está con nosotros, estamos felices de tenerlo.
世界上最好的前锋之一，所以当你身边有这样的球员时，情况总是更好。
one of the best strikers in the world, so when you have that kind of player on your side, it's always better.
uno de los mejores delanteros del mundo, así que cuando esa clase de jugadores lo tenés de tu lado, siempre es mejor.
你能向刚刚抵达马竞的朱利安和穆索传达什么信息？
What were you able to communicate to both Julián and Musso who have just arrived at Atlético?
¿Qué pudiste comunicarle tanto a Julián como a Musso que acaban de llegar al Atlético?
我认为他们很清楚马德里竞技是什么，这是一支庞大的球队。
I think they know well what Atlético de Madrid is, it is a giant team.
Creo que ellos saben bien lo que es el Atlético de Madrid, es un equipo gigante.
今年我们想要为我们所玩的一切而战。
in which this year we want to fight everything we play.
en el que este año queremos pelear todo lo que juguemos.
他们有很多责任，他们知道这一点，他们知道在那个水平上竞争是什么。
There are many responsibilities, they know it, they know what it is to compete at that level.
Hay muchas responsabilidades, ellos lo saben, ellos saben lo que es competir a ese nivel.
他们是拥有丰富经验、赢得过胜利的人。
They are guys who have a lot of experience, who have won things.
Son chicos que tienen mucha experiencia, que han ganado cosas.
剩下要做的唯一一件事就是帮助他们……
The only thing left to do is help them when it comes to...
Solo queda ayudarlos en lo que respecta al...
日复一日，因为与家人一起改变国家并不容易，但是嘿，你知道你总是在附近。
day to day because it is not easy to change countries with your family and all that, but hey, you know that you are always there nearby.
al día a día porque no es fácil cambiar de país con la familia y todo eso, pero bueno, sabe que uno está siempre ahí cerquita.
罗德里说，改变国家并不容易，有人告诉你，回到赛车吧。
Rodri said, it's not easy to change countries, someone just told you, go back to Racing.
Rodri decía, no es fácil cambiar de país, recién te dijo uno, volvé a Racing.
不久前我们看到了维耶托，有时虫子会咬人。
And a while ago we saw Vieto, the bug bites sometimes.
Y hace un rato lo vimos a Vieto, pica el bichito a veces.
嗯，我想我还年轻，我想享受......
Well, I think I'm still young, I want to enjoy...
Bueno, creo que todavía soy joven, quiero disfrutar de...
我在足球、国家队中留下的东西，我们也拥有的重要东西。
of what I have left in my football, in the national team, the important things that we also have.
de lo que me queda en mi fútbol, en la selección, las cosas importantes que también tenemos.
我在一家伟大的俱乐部，世界上最大的俱乐部之一。
I am in a great club, one of the biggest in the world.
Estoy en un grandísimo club, uno de los más grandes del mundo.
我享受这一切，我尽量不去想其他的事情。
I enjoy all that, I try not to think beyond it.
Disfruto de todo eso, intento no pensar más allá.
我知道...
I know that...
Sé que...
我知道我正在从事的职业并不容易，要实现这一切......
I know that the career I am doing is not easy and to achieve everything that...
Sé que la carrera que estoy haciendo no es fácil y para lograr todo lo que...
这意味着我的心态必须专注于日常工作。
What that means is that my mentality has to be focused on the day to day.
Lo que lleva eso, mi mentalidad tiene que estar puesta en el día a día.
生日快乐！
Happy Birthday!
¡Feliz cumpleaños!
生日快乐！
Happy Birthday!
¡Feliz cumpleaños!
我很高兴，真的。
I'm very happy, really.
Estoy muy contento, la verdad.
很自豪回到这里。
Proud to be back here.
Un orgullo de estar de vuelta acá.
撤回面条的制裁？
The sanctions for withdrawing the noodle?
¿Las sanciones para el retiro del fideo?
不，这是情感，这是另一个游戏。
No, it's emotion, it's another game.
No, es emoción, es otro partido más.
所以，好吧，我会离开它。
So, well, I'll leave it.
Así que, bueno, lo dejo.
你好，请问这是怎么回事？
Hello, what's going on?
Hola, ¿qué va?
我们刚刚抵达，与祖国的国家队一起来到这里是我的梦想，这是我一直梦想的，但现在什么也没有，现在可以享受了。
We just arrived, it is a dream to be here with the national team of my country, which I always dreamed of and nothing, now to enjoy.
Recién llegamos, es un sueño estar acá con la selección de mi país que siempre lo soñé y nada, ahora a disfrutar.
你是怎么发现的？
How did you find out?
¿Cómo te enteraste?
我在威尼斯比赛之前就知道了
I found out before the Venice game
Me enteré antes del partido de Venecia
塞缪尔给我打电话，这是意料之中的消息。
Samuel called me and it was expected news.
me llamó Samuel y fue una noticia esperada.
我非常喜欢它。
I enjoyed it very much.
La disfruté muchísimo.
我还没有和他说过话，现在我可能会和他在一起，聊一会儿。
I haven't spoken to him yet, now I'm probably going to be there with him and be able to chat for a while.
Todavía no he hablado con él, ahora seguramente voy a estar ahí con él y voy a poder charlar un rato.
他们曾经告诉过你一句话，记住这并没有到此结束。
There is a phrase that they once told you, remember that this does not end here.
Hay una frase que te dijeron alguna vez, acordate que esto no termina acá.
在我看来，既然第一个电话是针对国家成年队的，那么你最好告诉一下。
It seems to me that now that the first call was for the Senior National Team, it would be good for you to tell it.
me parece que ahora que la primera convocatoria era la Selección Mayor, estaría bueno que la cuentes.
是的，最终能够享受它始终是梦想。
Yes, in the end it is always the dream to be able to enjoy it.
Sí, al final es el sueño siempre de poderla disfrutar.
这个电话总是伴随着...
This call always with...
Esta convocatoria siempre con...
带着总是来到这里迎接世界冠军、两届美国冠军的责任，这是一个非常好的责任，嗯
with the responsibility of always coming here to the world champion, the two-time champion of America and that is a very nice responsibility, well
con la responsabilidad siempre de venir acá al campeón del mundo, al bicampeón de América y eso es una responsabilidad muy linda que bueno
我必须面对的。
that I have to face.
que tengo que afrontar.
是迭戈，对吧？
It was Diego, right?
Fue Diego, ¿no?
迭戈·里瓦拉加（Diego Ribarraga）告诉你这句话。
Diego Ribarraga who told you that phrase.
Diego Ribarraga que te dijo esa frase.
是的，事实上，我在智利大学和他有很多回忆，所以我很高兴。
Yes, the truth is that I have many memories with him at the U of Chile, so I am very happy.
Sí, la verdad es que tengo muchos recuerdos con él en la U de Chile, así que muy feliz.
塔蒂，当你看阿根廷国家队的时候，当你还是个孩子的时候，谁是你的镜子，你的偶像，你梦想成为谁？
Tati, when you watched the Argentine national team, when you were a child, who was your mirror, your idol, who did you dream of being?
Tati, cuando mirabas la selección argentina, cuando eras chico, ¿quién era tu espejo, tu ídolo, quién soñabas ser?
现在，穿着这件球衣的梦想成真了。
and now see this dream come true of wearing the shirt.
y ahora ver este sueño hecho realidad de vestir la camiseta.
国家队总是穿着伟大的球员。
The national team always dressed great players.
La selección siempre vistieron grandes jugadores.
作为一个孩子，我来自里奥那一代，显然是来自梅西。
As a child I am from Leo's generation, obviously from Messi.
Yo de chico soy de la generación de Leo, obviamente de Messi.
这是我的梦想，而事实是......
It's my dream and the truth is...
Es mi sueño y la verdad que...
很多球员，显然在我的位置上，也有很多球员都穿着这件球衣，但现在没有什么能够穿这件球衣了
that many players, obviously in my position, also many players wore it and nothing now to be able to wear this shirt
que muchísimos jugadores obviamente de mi posición también la vistieron muchísimos jugadores y nada ahora poder ponerme esta camiseta
这对你来说将是最美丽的事情。
and it will be the most beautiful thing for you.
y se te hará lo más lindo.
是的，让我们看看，现在的劳塔罗、朱利安，我认为现在的新一代......
Yes, let's see, nowadays Lautaro, Julián, who is currently, I think with the new generation that...
Sí, a ver, hoy en día Lautaro, Julián, que está en la actualidad, creo que con la generación nueva que...
他们现在已经赢得了一切。
who have won everything now.
que han ganado todo ahora.
一场特别的比赛，因为这将是对迪玛利亚的致敬，如果你第一次征召入队，你会如何看待。
A special match because it will be a tribute to Di María, how do you take that if your first call-up comes.
Un partido especial porque va a ser un homenaje para Di María, cómo tomás eso si viene tu primera convocatoria.
是的，嗯，对我来说这也是全新的，能够享受这个。
Yes, well, for me this is all new too, being able to enjoy this.
Sí, bueno, para mí todo esto es nuevo también, poder disfrutar esto.
不幸的是我没有机会和迪玛丽亚在一起，这也是另一个梦想，但我们将能够在那里享受它。
Unfortunately I don't have the opportunity to be with Di María, which was also another dream, but we will be able to enjoy it there.
Lamentablemente no tengo la oportunidad de poder estar con Di María, que también era otro sueño, pero lo vamos a poder disfrutar ahí.
以至于人们也
so much so that people also
tanto que la gente también
我很高兴他为这件球衣付出了一切。
I can enjoy that he has given everything with this shirt.
lo pueda disfrutar que lo ha dado todo con esta camiseta.
多次入围，但你从未获得过这次的机会。
shortlisted several times and you never got the opportunity that was given this time.
varias veces preseleccionado y nunca te tocaba la oportunidad que esta vez se dio.
好吧，我只是说，梅西不在，迪玛利亚不在，但我想无论如何，骄傲一定是一样的。
Well, I just said, Messi is not there, Di María is not there, but I imagine that pride must be the same anyway.
Bueno, recién decía, no está Messi, no está Di María, pero me imagino que el orgullo debe ser igual de todas maneras.
是的，是的，总是，显然。
Yes, yes, always, obviously.
Sí, sí, siempre, obviamente.
这是我必须享受的一件非常好的事情，我现在必须利用这个并不总是发生的机会。
It is something very nice that I have to enjoy, I have to take advantage now of this opportunity that does not always happen.
Es algo muy lindo que tengo que disfrutar, tengo que aprovechar ahora esta oportunidad que no siempre se da.
我必须充分利用这段时间，最重要的是享受这些日子并专注于国家队。
and I have to make the most of it and above all enjoy these days and be focused on the national team.
y tengo que aprovecharlo al máximo y sobre todo disfrutar estos días y estar enfocado en la selección.
一年半前加拉多想要你，现在斯卡罗尼又征召了你，你有什么反映？
A year and a half ago Gallardo wanted you, now Scaloni called you up, what reflection do you have?
Hace un año y medio te quiso Gallardo, ahora te convocó Scaloni, ¿qué reflexión te merece?
那种级别的教练会想到你。
Coaches of that stature think of you.
Entrenadores de esa talla piensen en vos.
非常好，非常好。
It's very nice, very nice.
Es muy lindo, muy lindo.
显然每当...
Obviously whenever...
Obviamente siempre que...
被谈论总是一件非常重要的事情。
Being talked about is always something very important.
que se hable de mí siempre es algo muy importante.
它让我个人成长很多，尤其是作为一个人。
It makes me grow a lot personally and especially as a person.
me hace crecer mucho en lo personal y sobre todo en lo persona.
像他们这样的技术人员注意到我，这对于继续成长非常重要。
That technicians like them notice me, that is very important to continue growing.
que técnicos como ellos se fijen en mí, eso es muy importante para seguir creciendo.
事实是我们很好，是的。
The truth is that we are fine, yes.
La verdad que estamos bien, sí.
周末...
The weekend...
El fin de semana...
我们从周四开始，事实是我本来可以没事的。
We started on Thursday, the truth is that I could have been fine.
Empezamos el jueves, la verdad es que pude estar bien.
足够的时间，我也能够进球，所以我也充满信心。
enough minutes, I was also able to score so I also come with confidence.
bastantes minutos, pude marcar también así que con confianza también vengo.
我在俱乐部表现很好，这很重要。
I'm doing well in my club, which is important.
vengo bien en mi club que es importante.
我说你来得正是时候，因为首先是对阵米兰的那粒进球。
You arrive at a good time, I say because of that goal against Milan above all.
Llegas en un buen momento digo por ese gol al Milan sobre todo.
是的，我不知道这是否是一个好时机，但我总是自信地说……
Yes, I don't know if it's a good time, but with confidence I always said that...
Sí, no sé si buen momento, pero sí con la confianza siempre dije que...
能够来到国家队，与你的球队共度美好时光，这真是太好了。
Being able to also come here to the National Team is good to come at a nice time with your team.
que poder venir también acá a la Selección está bueno venir en un momento lindo con tu equipo.
今天我想我已经做到了。
Today I think I have it.
Hoy en día pienso que lo tengo.
你和国家队谈过，当你很小的时候，五六岁……
You spoke with the national team and when you were very young, five or six years old...
Hablaste con la selección y cuando eras muy chiquito, cinco o seis años...
你们是由一位世界冠军带领的。
You were led by a world champion.
te dirigió un campeón del mundo.
莱奥波尔多·哈辛托·卢克（Leopoldo Jacinto Luque），这是多么好的反思，多么的观点。
Leopoldo Jacinto Luque, what a reflection, what an opinion.
Leopoldo Jacinto Luque, qué reflexión, qué opinión.
你对那段时间和那个特定时刻有什么记忆？
And what memories do you have of that time and that specific moment.
y qué recuerdos tenés de aquella época y de ese momento puntual.
是的，莱奥波尔多一直是一个……
Yes, Leopoldo was always a...
Sí, Leopoldo siempre fue una...
他始终是我的灵感来源。
He is always an inspiration to me.
Es una inspiración siempre para mí.
从小我就一直和他一起长大，和他一起踢足球。
Since I was a child I always grew up with him, along with him in football.
Desde chico siempre crecí con él, junto con él en el fútbol.
他就像我的父亲，事实是，这是一件非常好的事情，我从他那里学到的一切也都是
He was like my dad and the truth is that it was something very nice, everything I learned with him being also
fue como mi papá y la verdad que fue algo muy lindo todo lo que aprendí con él siendo también
代表这件衬衫。
having represented this shirt.
haber representado esta camiseta.
是的，让我们看看。
Yes, let's see.
Sí, a ver.
这很复杂，因为我们知道球员的所有体型。
It's complicated because we know all the sizes of players there are.
Es complicado porque sabemos todas las tallas de jugadores que hay.
在阿根廷，情况非常复杂，但是嘿，现在我必须享受它，来到这里，我必须利用它。
in Argentina and it is very complicated, but hey, now I have to enjoy it, be here and I have to take advantage of it.
en la Argentina y es muy complicado, pero bueno, ahora me toca disfrutar, estar acá y lo tengo que aprovechar.